Guide to the Yale College Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Yale College grade sheets, Fall 2003; Accession 2006-A-153
  - Egyptian, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Electrical Engineering, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - English, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Environmental Engineering, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Environmental Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - EMD (Epidemiology and Public Health), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Ethics Politics and Economics, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Ethnicity Race and Migration, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Film Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - French, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Genetics, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - German Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - GHD (Global Health), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Greek, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - HPA (Health Public Administration), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Hebrew, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Hellenic Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Hindi, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - History, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - History of Art, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Humanities, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Indonesian, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - International Relations, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - International Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Italian, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Japanese, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Judaic Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Korean, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Latin, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Latin American Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Law School, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Linguistics, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Literature, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Management, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Math, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Modern Greek, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - MBandB, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - MCDB, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Music, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Music School, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Near East Languages, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Neurobiology, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Persian, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Philosophy, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Physics, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Polish, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Political Science, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Portuguese, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Psychology, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Religious Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Renaissance Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Russian, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Russian and East European Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Science, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Serbian and Croatian, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Slavic Lang and Lit, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Sociology, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Spanish, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Special Divisional, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Statistics, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Teacher Prep, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Theater Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Turkish, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Vietnamese, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Women's and Gender Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 106)
- Student records for the Class of 1994, 1990-1994; Accession 2008-A-077
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2070
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1993, Accession 2013-A-004
  Restricted until January 1, 2078
- Student records for the Class of 1995, 1991-1995; Accession 2013-A-085
  Restricted until January 1, 2080
- Student records for the Classes of 1996-1998, 1992-1998; Accession 2014-A-020
  General
  The inclusive dates of the records are from 1991-1995 unless otherwise specified.
  - Class of 1996
  - Class of 1997
  - Class of 1998
- Student records for the Classes of 1999-2000, 1995-2000; Accession 2014-A-045
  Restricted until January 1, 2075
  - Class of 1999
  - Class of 2000
- Grades and enrollment data, 1957-2007; Accession 2016-A-050
  - Yale College 2008 Fall Grades
    - Accounting, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - African American Studies, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - African Studies, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - American Studies, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Anthropology, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Applied Math, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Arabic, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Archaeological Studies, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Architecture, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Art, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Astronomy, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Biomedical Engineering, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Chronic Disease Epidemiology, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Chemistry, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Chinese, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Child Studies, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Classic Civilization, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Computer Science, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Branford College Seminar, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Davenport College Seminar, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Timothy Dwight College Seminar, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Directed Studies, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Drama, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - East Asian Studies, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Economics, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Egyptology, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Electrical Engineering, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Epidemiology of Microbial Disease, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Environmental Engineering, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - English, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Ethics, Politics, Economics, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Ethnicity, Race, Migration, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Environmental Studies, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Film Media Studies, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Forestry Environmental Studies, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - French, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - German, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - German Studies, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Hindi, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - History, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - History of Art, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - History of Science and Medicine, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Humanities, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - International Studies, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Italian, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Japanese, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Latin, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Law, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Literature, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Math, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Molecular, Cellular Developmental Biology, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Management, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - School of Music, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilizations, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Philosophy, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Physics, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Political Science, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Portuguese, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Psychology, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Religious Studies, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Russian, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Science, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - South Asian Studies, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Sociology, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Spanish, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Special Term Course, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Statistics, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Theater Studies, 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Yale College 2009 Spring Grades
    - African Studies, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - African American Studies, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - American Studies, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Anthropology, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Applied Math, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Arabic, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Architecture, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Art, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Astronomy, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Biomedical Engineering, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Chemical Engineering, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Chemistry, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Chronic Disease Epidemiology, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Chinese, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Classical Civilization, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Cognitive Science, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - College Seminars, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Computer Science, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Directed Studies, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Divinity School Religion courses, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Drama, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Economics, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Electrical Engineering, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Egyptian, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - English, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Environmental Studies, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Ethics, Politics, Economics, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Ethnicity, Race, Migration, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Film Media Studies, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Forestry, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - French, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Geology and Geophysics, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - German, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Greek, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - History, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - History of Art, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - History Science Medicine, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Health Policy Administration, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Humanities, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Indonesian, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 115)
    - International Studies, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 116)
    - Japanese, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 117)
    - Judaic Studies, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 118)
    - Law, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 119)
    - Linguistics, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 120)
    - Literature, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 121)
    - Management, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 122)
    - Math, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 123)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 124)
    - Modern Middle East Studies, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 125)
    - Molecular, Cellular Developmental Biology, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 126)
    - Music, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 127)
    - Philosophy, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 128)
    - Physics, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 129)
    - Political Science, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 130)
    - Portuguese, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 131)
    - Psychology, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 132)
    - Religious Studies, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 133)
    - Russian, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 134)
    - Science, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 135)
    - Sociology, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 136)
    - Spanish, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 137)
    - Special Divisional Major, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 138)
    - Statistics, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 139)
    - Study of the City, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 140)
    - Theater Studies, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 141)
    - Vietnamese, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 142)
    - Women's Gender Sexuality Studies, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Yale College 2011 Fall Grades
    - Executive Committte Decisions, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 144)
    - Class of 2009 Senior Distribution, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 145)
    - Accounting, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 146)
    - African American Studies, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 147)
    - African Studies, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 148)
    - American Studies, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 149)
    - Anthropology, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 150)
    - Arabic, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 151)
    - Architecture, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 152)
    - Art, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 153)
    - Astronomy, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 154)
    - Archaeological Studies, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 155)
    - Biomedical Engineering, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 156)
    - Cell Biology, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 157)
    - Chemistry, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 158)
    - Chemical Engineering, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 159)
    - Chinese, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 160)
    - Classic Civilization, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 161)
    - Cognitive Science, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 162)
    - College Seminars, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 163)
    - Pierson College Seminar, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 164)
    - The DeVane Lecture Course, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 165)
    - Directed Studies, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 166)
    - East Asian Studies, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 167)
    - Ecology Evoloutionary Biology, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 168)
    - Economics, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 169)
    - Electrical Engineering, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 170)
    - Egyptology, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 171)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 172)
    - English, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 173)
    - Environmental Engineering, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 174)
    - Environmental Studies, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 175)
    - Ethics, Politics, Economics, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 176)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 177)
    - Film Media Studies, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 178)
    - Forestry Environmental Studies, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 179)
    - French, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 180)
    - Genetics, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 181)
    - Geology and Geophysics, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 182)
    - German, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 183)
    - Global Affairs, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 184)
    - Greek, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 185)
    - Health Studies, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 186)
    - History, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 187)
    - History of Art, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 188)
    - History of Science Medicine, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 189)
    - Health Policy Adminstration, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 190)
    - Humanities, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 191)
    - International Studies, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 192)
    - Italian, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 193)
    - Japanese, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 194)
    - Korean, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 195)
    - Latin, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 196)
    - Latin American Studies, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 197)
    - Law, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 198)
    - Linguistics, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 199)
    - Literature, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 200)
    - Management, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 201)
    - Math, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 202)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 203)
    - Modern Middle East Studies, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 204)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 205)
    - Molecular, Cellular Developmental Biology, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 206)
    - Music, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 207)
    - Music School, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 208)
    - Peking University, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 209)
    - Philosophy, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 210)
    - Physics, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 211)
    - Political Science, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 212)
    - Portuguse, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 213)
    - Psychology, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 214)
    - Religion (Divinity School), 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 215)
    - Religious Studies, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 216)
    - Russian, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 217)
    - Sociology, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 218)
    - Spanish, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 219)
    - Statistics, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 220)
    - Special Term Course, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 221)
    - Theater Studies, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 222)
    - Womens Gender Sexuality Studies, 2011 Fall (Box 1, Folder 223)
  - Yale College 2012 Spring Grades
    - Yale in China 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Accounting, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - African American Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - African Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Americian Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Anthropology, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Arabic, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Archaeological Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Applied Physics, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Architecture, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Art, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Astronomy, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Biomedical Engineering, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Chronic Disease Epidemiology, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Chemical Engineering, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Chemistry, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Chinese, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Cognitive Science, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - College Seminars, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Comparative Literature, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Computer Science, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Czech, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - The DeVane Lecture Course, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Drama, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Directed Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Dutch, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - East Asian Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Ecology Evoloutionary Biology, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Economics, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Electrical Engineering, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Enivronmental Health Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - English, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Ethics, Politics, Economics, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Ethnicity, Race, Migration, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Environmental Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Film Media Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Forestry Environmental Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - French, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - German, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Geology and Geophysics, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Global Affairs, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Greek, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Health Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - History, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - History of Art, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - History of Science Medicine, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Health Policy Adminstration, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Humanities, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Indonesian, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - International Relations, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - International Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Japanese, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Judaic Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Korean, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Linguistics, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Latin American Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Law, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Literature, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Math, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Management, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Music, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilization, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Neurobiology, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Neuroscience, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Philosophy, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Physics, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Political Science, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Portuguese, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Psychology, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Religious Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Russian, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Science, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Sociology, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - South Asian Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 80a)
    - Spanish, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Statistics, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Kiswahili, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Teacher Preparation, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Theater Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Women's Gender Sexuality Studies, 2012 Spring (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Yale College 2009 Fall Grades
    - School of Music, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Class of 2010 Distributional Requirements, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Accounting, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - African American Studies, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - African Studies, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - American Studies, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Anthropology, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Applied Math, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Archaeology, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Architecture., 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Art, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Astronomy, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Biomedical Engineering, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Chemical Engineering, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Chemistry, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Chinese, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Classic Civilization, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - College Seminars, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Cognitive Science, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Comparative Literature, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Computer Science, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Directed Study, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Divinity School, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Drama, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Economics, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Electrical Engineering, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - English, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Engineering Applied Sciences, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Environmental Studies, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Ethnicity, Race, Migration, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Ethics, Politics, Economics, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Film Media Studies, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Forestry Environmental Studies, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - French, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Geology and Geophysics, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Genetics, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - German, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Hindi, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - History, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - History of Art, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - History of Science Medicine, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Humanities, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - International, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Italian, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Japanese, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Latin, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 135a)
    - Law, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Linguistics, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Literature, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Management, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Math, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Molecular, Cellular Developmental Biology, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 144)